### **Jonathan Smith**

2309 Panhandle St Denton Tx, 76201 aardvarkjon@gmail.com

## Summary

Highly motivated individual and self taught web developer looking to join a development team. I have several years of IT experience, and I have experience with the work from home workflow. I am people oriented, a strong communicator, and have a love for learning and problem solving. With my self taught route, I have gained proficiency in problem solving and learning new technologies.

#### Skills

- Proficient with html
- Proficient with CSS
- Proficient with JavaScript

- Proficient with GIT/Github workflow
- Experience with the MERN/PERN stacks
- Some experience with Adobe XD

# **Work Experience**

# Working Solutions Denton Tx/Plano Tx Service Analyst

09/2019 - current

- Monitor and resolve agent technical issues via a Salesforce Ticket system in a timely manner via email responses
- Responsible for maintaining an effective level of communication to our internal team, as well as the client
- Troubleshoot multiple remote based systems including Citrix, VMWare, BrightPattern, and more
- Hosting live troubleshooting sessions through a WebEx training environment which involves either verbal coaching, or taking direct control of agent machines to troubleshoot their system
- Responsible for remote setup of new agents via WebEx Training to ensure they were ready and able to service our clients
- Remote troubleshooting of Windows based Operating systems

# Apple Inc. Southlake/Plano Tx 04/2018 – 09/2019 Genius

- Certified technician working on troubleshooting and repairing Apple devices, including Macs, mobile devices, Apple TV's etc.
- Experienced in breaking down problems and relating that to the customer in an empathetic way
- Responsible for leading our technicians on the floor and in repairs
- Experience with both Mac and Windows environments for software support

# **Apple Inc. Southlake Tx 07/2017 – 04/2018**

- Genius Admin
  - Handled paperwork and repair details
  - Responsible for bookkeeping in regards to repairs and inventory variance
  - Responsible leader in the repair room to communicate between technicians and leadership
  - Responsible to communicate with customers and inform them of their repair status
  - Experienced with hard conversations that require empathy and understanding to the customer

# Apple Inc. Southlake/Plano Tx 10/2015 – 07/2017

### **Apple Specialist**

- Responsible with helping customers make informed decisions and purchases
- Responsible with helping customer set up their device, and recover their previous information
- Responsible with communicating with the customer about their time in the store, whether it was for an appointment or for sales and directing them to the proper location
- Helped with the inventory management team to deliver product to team mates
- Helped with closing duties to ensure a clean and presentable store

#### **Education**

## **North Central Texas College**

08/2016 - 08/2017

Finished several certificates while working, including photoshop, illustrator and more Audited Django for Everybody from the University of Michigan through Coursera Currently taking the Full Stack Open course through the University of Helsinki(Finland)

### **Affiliations**

Leadership - F.O.C.U.S. Ministries(2015-2018) Member - F.O.C.U.S. Ministries(2014-2018)